That's it!
How does it look back there?
Give it to me straight, Fugo.
To be blunt, he did a number on you.
This is a real goose egg.
That hurts, dammit!
I asked you to take a look,
not make it more excruciating!
Pass di merda!
You gave me this fat knob on my noggin!
So it's only right that I make you suffer!
Getting attacked doesn't
feel so good, does it?
Well, too bad, here's some more!
Did you really think
you were better than us?
You limpty cazone!
Hmm?
Something fell off him.
Let's see.
Mario Zucchero says he's from Rome.
What's a Roman thug doing out here?
Yo, is that a piece of
trash stuck to your face?
On second thought, maybe
it's a piece of seaweed.
Yeah, I'd much rather it be seaweed,
but there's something about
it that screams plastic to me.
Gotta say, it pains my soul
to think it might be trash.
That means these beautiful waters
are teeming with pollution.
You're cool with me inspecting
the specimen. Right?
Hey, Butt Munch.
I asked to take a closer look
at that thing on your face.
You could at least have the common
decency to answer my question.
Capri.
Long ago, when the ancient Greeks
began to colonize the Mediterranean,
explorers sought out the most stunning
landscapes of the Great Cerulean Expanse.
Upon discovering the isle, they
knew they'd found their destination.
It is an area blessed with azure
waters and brilliant skies.
Steep ivory cliffs soar above the
sea like a single grand fortress.
One Roman emperor even built
private villas on the island,
where he remained until
his death 10 years later.
Now the mystifying locale sits
before Bruno Bucciarati and his crew.
Hidden on it, a dazzling
fortune worth 10 billion lira.
Thank you.
Bucciarati, we should map out our
route to the island, don't you think?
I've been on the lookout for a while now,
but I haven't spotted any more
enemies still trying to tail us,
and there's no way that anyone would
know this boat is heading to Capri.
All right, we're clear.
Still, I want to know who told that
bastard about the secret fortune.
The way he knew about our plans.
He had to have been working with someone.
Hmm.
You know, I noticed you've been
eyeing these things for a while now.
They're for sure not mine, so I'm not
really sure how they got on the boat.
Loser's choice, which one should I use?
The glasses or the fishing line?
If we don't get some answers out
of you, it's not gonna be pretty.
Your answers will help keep us
out of danger, so spill your guts.
You're not working alone, are you, Mr.
Zucchero?
Let me guess, your partner's a stand user.
Yep, that's why I'll be using these.
Still don't know which one
you want me to use, huh?
Well, if you can't decide,
I'll just have to use both and see
which one gets the best results!
How's that?
Now are you in the mood to chat?
Mario Zucchero.
Heaven, hell, purgatory.
Purgatory!
You lucked out, my man!
Looks like Purgatory it is!
If you won't fess up
about the name and powers
of your stalker friend
then I suppose we're
done you might want to
start worrying about
the well being of your
good eye hear what I'm
saying you bobble-headed turnt burglar how
long are you gonna dick
around idiots come look
at this he was using the
boat's radio so moody
jazz's replay found
something let's check it out
this boat may have been
flatter than a pizza
but now it's all back
to normal along with our
culprit here
Giorno
you
haven't earned my trust
yet so you don't get
the privilege of looking
turn around you're lucky
I'm even letting you
hear his voice his
replay clearly shows him
using the radio in the
cabin to contact someone
but I don't know who
hey I'm already holding
four of them hostage.
It's down to Bucciarati and the other guy.
I'll be done before you
can miss me.
Oh, and one more thing.
They're going to Capri.
They still haven't come out and...
Now what are we supposed to do?
The bastard hurt everything!
But once I get rid
of his bootlickers, I'll
make Zipper Boy squeal. Over.
What was the name of that yacht again?
Lagoon?
Also, identify your whereabouts.
We're about two hours away from landing on
Capri.
Bucciarati is trying to
lose potential pursuers
by taking a roundabout way to the island.
Understood.
I'll take a speedboat to
Capri and meet you there.
Kick Marina Grande.
Over and out.
It's done.
The radio cuts out after that.
Well, that's just perfect. Damn it!
That speedboat is gonna get him
to Capri in less than 30 minutes!
That means he's already on
the island. You're kidding.
Just who the hell was
that guy on the other end?
All right, no more games.
Time for this sunburned ballsack to
tell us exactly what we want to know.
No, he's a diehard mafioso.
Getting him to come clean
is going to take some time.
I doubt he'll be spilling his guts today.
Even if he did talk, we don't know
if he's seen his partner stand.
It's likely he kept it
a secret, even to him.
Then where does that leave us?
Let's just go to the
harbor and take him down.
Imagine what'll happen
if the guy finds out
Zuccaro isn't the only
one left on this boat.
Mista's right.
We have to hurry.
We only have an hour to get
the boat to Marina Grande.
If we don't, the guy on the radio will
think something happened to Zuccaro.
Once that happens, we can
kiss that fortune goodbye.
No.
We'll be lucky to make it
back to Napoli in one piece.
It's your call. What's next?
Indecision isn't an option.
We have to take action
and outsmart our opponent.
I have to make it to that island before...
Now before this boat docks...
Someone needs to scout ahead.
Taking this guy out
first is our best option.
Just what the hell are you
yammering on about, newbie?
You must be a freaking
idiot if you think one of
us can get to the island
faster than this boat.
How would we even do that? Swim? Yes. Huh?
I'll use my stand to turn
this buoy into a fish.
Believe me, it can pull someone
along faster than this boat can sail.
Don't worry.
It's my stand, so I'll go.
Nothing is going to get
in the way of my dream.
I want that ten billion.
We'll use it to make Bucciarati a Cape.
We'll use the money to work
our way up through the Family.
Sure now.
Hey, you got a death wish?
Then knock yourself out!
You've dreamt up some clever idea, boy.
Too bad you don't have a clue as
to his name or what he looks like.
And the port of Capri is
crawling with lots of tourists.
How do you think you're gonna
fight him in a crowd of peacockers?
You know what?
I'm actually with Giorno on this one.
So we don't know the
identity of this asshole.
Big deal.
If he's waiting for Zuccaro
to arrive in this boat,
then I think we've got a fighting chance.
We gotta take it, no
matter what the risk is.
Why wait for him to make his move?
The bastard won't know what hit him.
So, about that fish.
How many people can it take, Giorno?
My stand, Six Bullets, is
specifically designed to kill.
Which means they're more than
up for this little mission.
Just leave it to us.
Swimming over here from the boat
took a bit longer than I expected.
We only have 20 minutes before the
meeting with our men of mystery.
Let's hurry.
We need to finish the job quickly.
Giorno, how's it looking from the marina?
Not that great.
Bakio wasn't kidding.
There are tourists everywhere.
They all seem to be waiting for someone.
Of course, most of them are waiting
for arriving ships. But still?
Signore, we only have 20
minutes to weed this guy out.
Do you have a plan on how we're
going to do that, or do we improvise?
What the hell are you doing?
I take it you haven't noticed
it's way past lunchtime?
What I'd really like to do is
go to that restaurant there!
But everyone knows the
restaurants right on
the water serve that shitty touristy crap.
I don't have any idea
what the enemy looks like.
But I'm guessing he
wouldn't be able to say the
same for me since I'm a
member of Bucciarati's team.
Eddie's seen your face by now too.
Sorry, but I'm not following
your train of thought.
If I can speak my mind for a sec!
I know I said we had 20 minutes left,
but if he's a worrywart, we might
only have 10 minutes to get him.
Five if he gets antsy.
He may get suspicious when
the lagoon fails to arrive,
and catch on to the fact that
something shady happened to Zucchero.
If that happens, our man
will go off the grid.
We can't waste another
minute sitting around
- What part of lunch break don't you get?
It's lunchtime now, so I'm eating lunch.
Go to any boutique or bookstore in
this country and you'll find out.
No one can work on an empty stomach. Huh?
I mean, I'm obviously nothing like that.
But these little fellas take
the custom pretty seriously.
Settle down now, you'll
all get your num-nums.
Salame toscano e Bone!
Yummy!
Hey, get me some of that!
Come on, number three,
knock it off already!
You're hogging the meat
and making number five cry.
Enough of the bickering.
There's plenty of food for everyone.
Each one thinks he works the hardest,
so each one thinks he deserves
the most food when it's chow time.
I make it a point to ensure
no one gets left out.
Easy, number five.
You can't keep crying about everything.
So what's the deal, Mista?
How many of those things do you have?
Hey, don't call them things.
It's rude.
They get really irritated
when you treat them like pets.
There are six of them,
but you won't find a number four
because it brings nothing but bad luck.
I have one of these guys for
each of the bullets in my gun.
But what for?
Hate to break up the party, but
this guy wants us to get a move on.
It sure would be nice if you guys could
take your nap after you finish the job.
Hey!
Quit it, number three!
What did I just say about hitting? Mista.
I know what you're gonna say,
but I'll get him on task.
We should get started.
Do me a favor and grab the
radio out of that bag there.
Once we're done working, it's gobble time!
It's balls to the walls, you guys!
Pay attention.
I'm going to make my way
to the guard shack and
use its shadow to conceal
myself from peering eyes.
Can I please have your attention
calling all passengers at the lagoon?
Any lagoon passengers out there?
We have a message from Signore Zuccaro.
Please make your way to the
guard shack on the double.
I repeat, calling all
passengers at the lagoon.
We have a message from Signore Zuccaro
that requires your immediate attention.
So he's playing it safe and
ignoring the announcement.
Or he thinks they've found the loot,
and he's about to jump out and
celebrate being 10 billion lira richer.
It's all a gamble.
Whoever hears the
announcement and heads to the
guard shack to get their
message is our mystery man.
I'm counting on you, Giorno.
If anyone makes a move toward
the guard shack, give me a sign.
Whoever answers that call is
going to get a head full of lead.
Then again, Bucciarati wants that ass
alive, so I should avoid his vitals.
We'll see how that goes.
Crap.
No one wants to make a move.
No one's heading over.
ATTENCIONE!
THIS IS THE LAST CALL!
CALLING ALL PASSENGERS OF THE Lagoon!
WE HAVE A MESSAGE FROM SENIOR
EZUCERO THAT REQUIRES YOUR ATTENTION!
NO ONE YET!
NOTHING'S HAPPENING!
HE'S GOTTA BE ON THE ISLAND SOMEWHERE!
COULD HE REALLY BE PLAYING
IT SAFE AND HIDING OUT?
Hey, Zookero, if something happened,
why did you request an announcement?
Is there a problem?
Over.
What is going on?
No one's showing up at the damn shack.
What?
He's inside.
But when did he...
That lookout must have another entrance.
And that bastard knew
exactly where it was.
It's too dark to see his face,
and Mista hasn't noticed him.
If things don't turn around, he'll
catch on to our ruse and run.
I have to let Mista know.
What?
The guy from the radio is finally coming?
Which one is it?
Who's coming to the lookout, Chaka?
No, Mista!
No one's going to the lookout!
He's already inside!
Just stay put!
The enemy is by the window!
This bastard!
He's one of Bucciarati's goons!
Zucchero was supposed to get rid
of him while he was on that boat!
Mista! Behind you!
The target is on the radio!
Mista! Damn it! He can't hear me!
I've got no choice!
On your left! Mista!
He's already on the radio!
Come on, pass, pass, pass!
Right.
Now go, six bullets.
Here we go!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
Yeah! Did he get him? Uh-huh.
Ugh.
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Also, what was that noise? Gunshots.
Sorry, did I disturb you?
Because I'm sure it wasn't as bad
as anything you hear in the movies.
But if my work really
disturbed your day...
I'm in the middle of something right now,
and I'll address all your
complaints once I'm done.
Giorno's always in a hurry.
Rear entrance, huh?
He must have made his way in through that
door in order to use the radio unnoticed.
Either he's taking caution
to a whole new level?
or the sneaky bastard has a weird habit.
of always trying to enter
buildings on the down low.
Regardless, that was some
killer work, Buds! Yay! Come on!
We got his leg!
We got that right leg good, didn't we?
Yeah, I'd say you nailed the sucker.
He's not going anywhere.
The usual tourists out front.
Back here is a friggin' cliff.
No way he climbed that thing!
Must be stumbling around here somewhere.
Show yourself, coward!
He must be hiding in that truck.
If he's a stand user,
then he's more than likely a
close-range one with striking power.
If he were the long-range type,
it's safe to say he would have
attacked me a long time ago.
Now that he's got a bum leg, he's not
going to be traveling any kind of distance,
so he's probably laying a trap for me.
I bet he's behind this truck
waiting to lure me in for the kill.
Well, it's not like he could
hurt me even if I did get close.
He's probably just beyond there.
But I'm still in the dark as
far as what his stand can do.
Going in without backup would
be risky, to say the least.
I should wait for Giorno and...
Shit.
Guess that option's out.
So the Strontos in the driver's seat.
He must have jump-started the engine.
I can't let him escape
now, especially here.
Damn this prick!
I still don't know what the guy
looks like, and neither does Giorno!
His stand will have to
stay a mystery for now.
This is for the 10 billion and Bucciarati!
Die!
Mista.
Every time I close my eyes.
I wake up feeling so horny.
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see.
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
I need your mind.
Tonight you got my time.
I'll give it to you.
Tonight you won't be sorry.
Tonight you got my mind.
I've got my mind, all I
want to do is free to you.
What must I say?
Tell me.
What must I do?
To show how much I'm going to free to you.
What must I say?
What must I do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
To show how much I'm going to free to you.
I'm gonna break it.
Thank you.